Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
David	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	David vander Put, Inwoonder der Stadt Maestricht
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Put	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Inwoonder	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Inwoonder der Stadt Maestricht
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Stadt Maestricht
Maestricht	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxprimeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Committimus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeesters	B-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Burgermeesters
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
geswooren	B-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	geswooren Raden der Stadt Maestricht
Raden	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Maestricht
Maestricht	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereleveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vonnis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contumaciam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negligentien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versuymen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepleeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsulcken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dato	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vonnisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
defauten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
decreten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gerechte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geadmitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
defensie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
justificatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijner	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onnoselheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
refunderende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
retardementen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Committimus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeesteren	B-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Burgermeesteren
ende	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
geswooren	B-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	geswooren Raden der Stadt Maestricht
Raden	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Maestricht
Maestricht	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
