Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitein	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capitein
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Kinsbergen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boord	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	's Lands Fregat Argo
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Lands	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Fregat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Argo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
27	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	27 der voorleeden maand
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
voorleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mallaga	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Mallaga
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaddresseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Griffier	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Griffier
Fagel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reiser	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Reiser van Marocco
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Marocco	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Marocco
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gechargeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Meesters	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onbewust	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweesen	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	geweesen Consul
Consul	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rossignol	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconsidereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul
Blount	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelast	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vlag	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lang	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waayen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Consul
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
30	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	30 Maart
Maart	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienaangaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevreest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reiser	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Reiser
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eigenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maakende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewoonte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretensie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
armen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweesenen	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	geweesenen Consul
Consul	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rossignol	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Land	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wilde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
