Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Anthony	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Anthony Reidt de Salis, Major van het Regiment Grisons van den Collonel Reidt
Reidt	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Salis	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Major	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Major van het Regiment Grisons van den Collonel Reidt
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	I-HOE	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regiment Grisons van den Collonel Reidt
Grisons	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Collonel	B-HOE	O	B-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collonel
Reidt	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallogeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongeluckige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toestandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gunstige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consideratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ander	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguleeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijner	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
achterstallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
provisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaare seventien hondert aght
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aght	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Obligatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zeeckere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bepaalde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termynen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alzoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soulagement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
magh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toestandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochmaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effhicacicuse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyze	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staaten van Utrecht
Staaten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Utrecht	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schryven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewenschte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wezen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedtgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hecren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hecren Staaten van Utrecht
Staaten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Utrecht	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochmaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerepraesenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compagnie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerepartieert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Utrecht
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Utrecht	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
minste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beswaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nergens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochtegevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ander	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fonds	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochmaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
considereeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hardt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
billijckheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanloopende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lange	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te-laaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaatse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belooninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
getrouwe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diensten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ruine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontmoeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolghlijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnoch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supphhaant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deughdelijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghterstallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eyndelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
minste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redelijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termynen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
