Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Berckel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pniladelphia	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Pniladelphia
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	4 der gepasseerde maand November
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
gepasseerde	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
November	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaddresseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Griffier	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Griffier
Tragel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Jesfersun, Minister der buitenlandsche zaaken
Jesfersun	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Minister	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Minister der buitenlandsche zaaken
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
buitenlandsche	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
zaaken	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinformeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Short, als Minister Resident by haar Hoog Mog
Short	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Minister	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Minister Resident by haar Hoog Mog
Resident	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
by	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
haar	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tytel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaats	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegeschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebrek	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vriedschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respeët	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lsoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Prassident	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Prassident der vereenigde Sraaten
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereenigde	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	vereenigde Sraaten
Sraaten	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeend	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deeze	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erreur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
corrigeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
substitueeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarschynlyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Short
Short	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uitvoeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particuliere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lsof	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	lsof van Madrid
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Madrid	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Madrid
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alvoorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	's Hage
s	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hage	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
konde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
arriveerren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begeerig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erreur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uitstel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
corrigeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer lefferson
lefferson	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzogt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hloog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toekomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dezelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ook	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoegt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
byvo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ging	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzeekeringen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeligheid	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vriendschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betoend	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Short	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Short
inmidddels	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deszelfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualiteit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erkennen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
20	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	20 Juny des gepasseerden jaars
Juny	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
gepasseerden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
jaars	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credentiaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Short
Short	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergadering	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
preesideerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nutulen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
20	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	20 Juny lLatstleeden
Juny	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
lLatstleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermerd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uitgewisseld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nieuwe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credentiaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laaste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebruikelyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyze	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewaard	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
