Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaques	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jaques Wyts Superintendent vande hooge crychsraet
Wyts	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Superintendent	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Superintendent vande hooge crychsraet
vande	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
hooge	I-HOE	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	hooge crychsraet
crychsraet	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerinne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhaelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ouer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bedieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
32	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
getracteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	heeren vanden Tempel ende du Bois
vanden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Tempel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
du	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bois	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
za	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bedieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliberatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tractement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
32	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inganck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
9	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	9. deses
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Generaliteit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vuyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ontfanger	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ontfanger generael
generael	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
namaels	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
comen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resterende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gul	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochtoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oorloch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerepartieert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cesseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertraordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toelech	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevoorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoMo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegevoucht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daertoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretenderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
