Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WVergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wern	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Wern. W. Cusp. Fabricius, by haar Hoogh Mogende aangestelt tot Predikant by der selver Minister in Spaigne
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
W	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Cusp	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Fabricius	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
by	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	by haar Hoogh Mogende aangestelt tot Predikant by der selver Minister in Spaigne
haar	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aangestelt	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Predikant	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
by	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
selver	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Minister	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Minister in Spaigne
in	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Spaigne	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Spaigne
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornemens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derwaarts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omnes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Populos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bestaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koffers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lijf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geRhoorende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedtgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omnes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Populos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Equipage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koffers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Madrid	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Madrid
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reysen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vry	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerechtigheydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
