Lie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reedenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jeegenwoordige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permoveesende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Administrateurs	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Administrateurs van het Colleyie te Auryck
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Colleyie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Auryck	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Auryck
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dispensatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beëedighde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verplightinghi	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaar	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaar seeventien honderd vyf en vyftigh
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepermitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	'eersten January en eersten July aanstaande
eersten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
January	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
eersten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
July	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aanstaande	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
geene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aflossingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guarantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Republicq	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genegotieert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noghtans	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exacte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sorge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
draagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Renten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onkosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeide	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termynen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boovengeroerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitaalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
promptelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overgebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geenderhande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorsaacke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consequeutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
getrocken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geheel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onvermindert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
solemneel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verband	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
origineele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conventie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestipuleert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verwaghtingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diergelijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sullende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rescriptie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Administrateurs	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Administrateurs van het Collegie te Auryck
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Auryck	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Auryck
kennis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
