Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Andries	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Andries Pauwels, Proost van de exempte Abdy van St. Pieter neevens Gent
Pauwels	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Proost	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Proost van de exempte Abdy van St. Pieter neevens Gent
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
exempte	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Abdy	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
St	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Pieter	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
neevens	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Gent	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Gent
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Plaatsen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Polders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vlaanderen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vlaanderen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ternitvir	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
administreeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abxye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toebehoorende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sieckte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ander	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodsaackelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Leeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abdye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduurende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaatse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mooge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekleeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguleerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Placaaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Roomsche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geestelijckheyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëmaneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onpasselijckheyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Leeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abdye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooriijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepecheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Plaatsen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Polders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vlaanderen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vlaanderen
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ressorterende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
telkens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verrightinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
affaires	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abdye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguleerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Placaaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Roomsche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geestelijckheyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geemaneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
