Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magistraat	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Magistraat der Stadt en Lande van Biervliet
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt en Lande van Biervliet
en	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Biervliet	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertighsten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	dertighsten der voorlede maandt
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
voorlede	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
klachten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermeynen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van Vlaanderen
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vlaanderen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vlaanderen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seecker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
interdictie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
poenaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sekeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adriaan	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Adriaan Goverts
Goverts	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magistraat	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Magistraat
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sequester	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Sequester
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangesteldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boedel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sekeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jan	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jan de Smith
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Smith	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alles	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
interdictie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
poenaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
trecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangestelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sequester	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Sequester
mocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gequalificeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontgonne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
proceduyren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
liquidatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boedel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wylen	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	wylen
gemelden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Jan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Smith	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
voort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Partyen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehoort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neutrale	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	neutrale Rechtsgeleerden
Rechtsgeleerden	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geinteresseerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boedel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
administreren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Justitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemoede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyvende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oordeelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beswaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
appel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rade	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Rade van Vlaanderen
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vlaanderen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vlaanderen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geestablisseerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cours	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
justitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rade	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
