Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ls	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Egbert	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Egbert Buys, Koopman tot Amsterdam
Buys	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Koopman	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Koopman tot Amsterdam
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guarnisoenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingezetenen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ingezetenen tot Meenen ende Cortreyck
tot	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Meenen	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Meenen ende Cortreyck
ende	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cortreyck	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derwaerts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
honderdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tarwe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rogge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Garste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Haver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Granen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diversse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hollandtsche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gent	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gent
derwaerts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beducht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schippers	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Schippers Gilde tot Gent
Gilde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gent	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Gent
difficulteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Granen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nederlandtsche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overschepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
groote	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belemmeringh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sware	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onkosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negotie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veroorsaecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ware	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permitteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gent	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gent
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pleyt-Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
avier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Granen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rechten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Granen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cortrijck	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Cortrijck ende Meenen
ende	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Meenen	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytvoeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
