Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coslegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Coslegie ter Admiraliteyt op de Maaze
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Maaze	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rotterdam	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Rotterdam
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aght	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	aght en twintighsten deeser loopende maand
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twintighsten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deeser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt in Wesftvriesland en het Noorder Quartier
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Wesftvriesland	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Noorder	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Quartier	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
geinformeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geworden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
muyterye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Volck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Houtingh	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beneevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Meyden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Praesenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dey	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Dey van Algiers
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Algiers	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Algiers
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
continueerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ernstiger	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
constrainte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dempen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alvoorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werckstelligh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemaackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereysschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
absolut	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onmoogelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Houtingh	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeven	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	seeven en twintighsten deeser
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twintighsten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deeser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zeyldagh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kiesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt op de Maaze
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Maaze	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
informeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedvinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt op de Maaze
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Maaze	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Meyden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Houtingh	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zeylen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gearresteerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zeyldagh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reeds	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepasseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wind	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Instiuctie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kiesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Seheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Presenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelaaden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Texel	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Texel
afgehaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zeylen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiers	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Algiers
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Houtingh	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zulcken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevalle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Meyden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
credentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dey	B-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Dey
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Regeeringe	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Algiers	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Algiers
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geworden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt op de Maaze
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Maaze	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerescribeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Meyden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wind	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kiesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Texel	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Texel
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gekoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinformeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
apparentelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zaacken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoodanigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Houtingh	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Instructie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reys	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voortsetten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onverhoopentlijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
alsdan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteynen ter Zee
ter	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saamen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
roepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overleggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguleeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevorderingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
intentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reys	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Meyden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
zullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
