Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Antwerpen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Antwerpen
behoorden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geauthoriseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevalle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeyelijckheden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
collusien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemoet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opsichte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteynen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Matrosen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Matrosen
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lillo	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lillo
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sclve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schicken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorkominge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongemacken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongenoegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onvermindert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rangh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerapporteerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	Heeren van Broeckhuysen
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Broeckhuysen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rangh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Zee- ende Landt-Officieren, aen Landt
-	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt-Officieren	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
examineren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consideratien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gecommitteerden	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Gecommitteerden van de Collegien ter Admiraliteyt
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alles	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienonvermindert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren haer Hoogh Mogende Gedeputeerden te Antwerpen
haer	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Antwerpen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Antwerpen
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengeschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteynen ter Zee
ter	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie van gisteren
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
gisteren	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	gisteren
vermelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lillo	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lillo
aengekomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derwaerts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerden
Gedeputeerden	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
traghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disputen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeyelijckheden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rangh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteynen ende de Officieren van de Landt-Militie
ende	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt-Militie	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doenlijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
employ	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteynen
soodanig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schicken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contesten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
collusien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ondienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee-Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Zee-Capiteynen
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
employeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Volck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Volck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
detachementen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebruycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteynen
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
employeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
posten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
competentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaetse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andersints	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oordeelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
best	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verachteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee-Capiteynen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Zee-Capiteynen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerden
Gedeputeerden	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oordeelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
al	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
grooten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ondienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschieden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
