Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehoord	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	Heeren van Nagell
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Nagell	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
zaaken	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie commissoriaal van den 19 October laatstleeden
commissoriaal	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	19 October laatstleeden
October	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
laatstleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxamineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteit te Amsterdam
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteit	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	16 daar te vooren
daar	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitein	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capitein
Reintjes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overgezonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coilegie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebragt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opbrengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant
vanden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Broek	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
commandeerende	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	commandeerende 's Lands Goulerte Flora
'	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	's Lands Goulerte Flora
s	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Lands	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Goulerte	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Flora	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Americaansche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brik	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
egter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontvlugt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naderhand	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hernomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorval	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant
vanden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Broek	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overgelegt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hehbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitein	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capitein
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vryheid	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
merken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wenschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee-Officieren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Zee-Officieren
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeringe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sluykhandel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gezonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duidelyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zevls	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaartuig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Handel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelaaden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
honden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
judicatuure	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanmerking	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
interessant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgekoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afzyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
develve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overlegging	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bylaage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennisle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoogst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedvinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehonoreert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
commissoriaal	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
28	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	28 October laatstleeden
October	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
laatstleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiralitet in Zeeland
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiralitet	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Zeeland	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Middelburg	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Middelburg
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	10 daar te vooren
daar	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitein	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capitein
H	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Reintjes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
commandeerende	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	commandeerende ter Rheede van Rio Demerary
ter	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rheede	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Rheede van Rio Demerary
van	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rio	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Demerary	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dato	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	8 July jongstleeden
July	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
jongstleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	de Lieutenant vanden Broek, commandeerende 's Lands Goulette de Fora
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant
vanden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Broek	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
commandeerende	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	commandeerende 's Lands Goulette de Fora
'	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	's Lands Goulette de Fora
s	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Lands	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Goulette	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Fora	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	2 te vooren
te	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongebragt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Americaansche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Americaansche Brik genaamt Eilzabeth
Brik	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
genaamt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Eilzabeth	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schipper	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schipper
D	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Wilson	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kust	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Kust van Demerary, voor de Courbane Rivier
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Demerary	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Courbane	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rivier	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
circa	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mylen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Anker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vond	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aannadering	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tragte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontvlugten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaane	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
visitatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Baalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Catoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daags	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rivier	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Rivier van Demerary
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Demerary	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pitgeklaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Caroen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boord	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omstandig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie-Rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant sub Litt
sub	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Litt	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoegt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bovengenoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitein	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capitein
Reintjes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodzaakelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ware	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	's Lands Zee-Officieren
s	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee-Officieren	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weering	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Handel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gezonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duidelyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorzien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
einde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaartuig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Handel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boord	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
najaagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opbrengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
judicatuure	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteit
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteit	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoedigsten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorzien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
En	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zaak	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Demerary	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Demerary
voorgevallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodzaakelykheid	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eener	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoedige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorzieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
encouragement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuiting	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
agterhaaling	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sluikhandel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colonie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Smokkelaar	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Smokkelaar
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
openbaare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niemand	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
offensie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
word	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deezen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lands Officieren
Officieren	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vry	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Smokkelaars	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Smokkelaars in de Westindiën
in	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Westindiën	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Westindiën
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
openbaare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Possessien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kusten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lang	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dezelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
agterhaalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zorge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dragende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kusten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermyden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegronde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
klagten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onthoudende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
distantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
myl	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kusten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Etablissementen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Europeesche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogendheeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dezelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pleegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteit in Zeeland
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteit	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Zeeland	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangaat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gezonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heeren van Grovestins
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Grovestins	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Grovestins en Boey
en	O	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Boey	O	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Commissarissen	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Commissarissen na de Westindische Eilanden
na	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Westindische	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Westindische Eilanden
Eilanden	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
einde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
retour	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Westindiën	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Westindiën
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
informeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zelver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consideratien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gezonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respective	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegien ter Admireliteit deezer Landen
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admireliteit	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
deezer	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Officieren
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ressorteerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
orders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conform	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
