Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
DY	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumtie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gecommitteerden	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Gecommitteerden van de respective Collegien ter Admiraliteyt
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
respective	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	haar Hoogh Mogende Resolutie van den neegenden April laastleeden
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
neegenden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	neegenden April laastleeden
April	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
laastleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schriftelijk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt in Zeeland
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Zeeland	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Middelburgh	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Middelburgh
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	derden Mey seeventien honderd vyf en dertigh
Mey	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
clucidatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgevaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derwaarts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
retourneeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schippers	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Schippers
toegesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nieuws	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Advisen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegien ter Admiraliteyt op de Maze, tot Amsterdam, in Westfriesland en het Noorder Quartier, en in Friesland
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Maze	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Westfriesland	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Noorder	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Quartier	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Friesland	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeventienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	seeventienden en vyf en twintighsten Mey, tienden Juny, en dertienden July seeventien honderd vyf en dertigh
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twintighsten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Mey	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
tienden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Juny	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
dertienden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
July	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respective	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegien ter Admiraliteyt
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geauthoriseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geauthoriscert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Onderdaanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgevaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevindende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permitteeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geval	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
destinatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelight	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
destinatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	haar Hoogh Mogende Resolutie van den vierden January seeventien honderd seevem en twintigh
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
vierden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	vierden January seeventien honderd seevem en twintigh
January	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
seevem	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
suppleeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reeders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geobligeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gekreegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
destinatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gekoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretarye	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Secretarye van het Collegie
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelight	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cautie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanteekenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cas	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nalaatigheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boete	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Borgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanspreekelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
En	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegien ter Admiraliteyt
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gequalificeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gequalificeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Onderdanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevindende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrocken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Onderdaanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welckers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduurende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reysen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
booven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaarem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oud	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geworden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Placaat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vierden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	vierden January seeventien honderd seeven en twintigh
January	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeven	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reeders	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Reeders
nakoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatstgemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uitgegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesuivert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgesondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaatse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resideeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ministers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consuls	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geval	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ministers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consuls	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overgeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiersche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schippers	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Schippers
overgegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ministers	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ministers
behoorlijk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doorgesneeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
