Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Item	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commis	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Commis
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zutphen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Zutphen
mette	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
thien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ouer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Henrick	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Henrick Schouten Contrerolleur vande fortificatie wercken tot Sutphen
Schouten	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Contrerolleur	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Contrerolleur vande fortificatie wercken tot Sutphen
vande	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
fortificatie	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
wercken	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Sutphen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Sutphen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
byden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seluen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Joncker	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Joncker
Johan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Dorth	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Raedt van State
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
State	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
geemployeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fortificatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
„	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vijhem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	heeren Staten Generael
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Generael	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedts	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedts van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
bestayet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bestaden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
