Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehoort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	Heeren van Essen
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Essen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Militaire	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie commissoriael van verscheyde datis
commissoriael	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
verscheyde	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
datis	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxamineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Krygsgevangenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlof	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
woort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vranckrijck	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vranckrijck
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlof	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Langon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
St	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	St. Viance, Capiteyn van de Grenadiers, in het Regiment van den Collonel de St. Germain Beaupre
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Viance	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn van de Grenadiers, in het Regiment van den Collonel de St. Germain Beaupre
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Grenadiers	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
in	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Collonel	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Collonel de St. Germain
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
St	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	St. Germain
.	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Germain	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Beaupre	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant
Jean	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bloy	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Marquiny	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaques	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jaques Paniville, Gendarme de Berry
Paniville	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Gendarme	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Gendarme de Berry
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Berry	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'haren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geregistreert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretarye	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Secretarye van den Raedt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
