Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ls	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Alexander	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Alexander Baron de Klinghspoor
Baron	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Baron de Klinghspoor
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Klinghspoor	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Klinghspoor
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sententie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kryghsrade	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Kryghsrade van Mulheym
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Mulheym	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Mulheym
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
woorden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
altoos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecasseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effecte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
infamie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gealtereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mngen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoegh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beright	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
favorabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereerdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedtgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
getreden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienvolgende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afgewesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
