Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maurits	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Maurits Grave van Nassau-Auerquercq, Generaal Major ende Commandant van Yperen
Grave	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Grave van Nassau-Auerquercq, Generaal Major ende Commandant van Yperen
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Nassau-Auerquercq	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Nassau-Auerquercq
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Generaal	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Major	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Commandant	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Yperen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Yperen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekomeen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Engelandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Engelandt
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ophouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxpireert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indispositie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrouw	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afdoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pressante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
affaires	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdtrequireerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Engelandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Engelandt
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ophouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliick	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlof	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Engelandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Engelandt
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ophouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
