Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Simon	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Simon Adriaan de Vries, Officier van de Vryheyt Oosterhout
Adriaan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vries	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Officier	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Officier van de Vryheyt Oosterhout
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vryheyt	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Vryheyt Oosterhout
Oosterhout	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Luurentius	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Luurentius Bax, Schoutet der Heerlijckheyt de Hage
Bax	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Schoutet	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schoutet der Heerlijckheyt de Hage
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Heerlijckheyt	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heerlijckheyt de Hage
de	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hage	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Baronnie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Baronnie van Breda
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Breda	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie van den veertienden November seventien hondert dertien
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
veertienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	veertienden November seventien hondert dertien
November	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
dertien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Officieren
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghterhalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vagabonden	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vagabonden
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Quaadtdoenders	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Quaadtdoenders
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verscheyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Placaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëmaneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verslappen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praemie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhooght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
provisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolgelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
expireren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaar	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaar seventien hondert vyftien
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyftien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praemie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cesseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
atigmentatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praemie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sedert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxpireerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgedruckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
continueren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedtvinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ontfanger	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ontfanger der verpondingen tot Breda
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verpondingen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Breda	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Breda
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordonneren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaugmenteerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praemie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geattrappeerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vagabonden	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vagabonden
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Placaaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgedruckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sedert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxpireerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
