Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
DE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gecommitteerden der Stadt Utrecht
Gecommitteerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Utrecht
Utrecht	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingebracht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Principalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sevenden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	sevenden Maart seventien hondert achtien
Maart	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
achtien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconformeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sentimenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorstemmende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Leden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twaalfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	twaalfden November seventien hondert sestien
November	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
sestien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geuyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanlangende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Duytsche	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Duytsche ende Fransche Gemeente te Hanover
ende	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Fransche	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gemeente	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Hanover	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hanover
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exemptie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belastinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Generaliteyts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
renten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebracht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
capitaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Comptoir	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Comptoir van de Generaliteyt
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Generaliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
geconstitueert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Edele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenparigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gecommitteerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authoTiseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geauthoriseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gecommitteerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie den eersten September seventien hondert sestien
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
eersten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	eersten September seventien hondert sestien
September	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
sestien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
vervat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Obligatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Duytsche	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Duytsche en Fransche Gemeente tot Hanover
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Fransche	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gemeente	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Hanover	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hanover
(	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toebehoorende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reductie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
15	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van de Provincie van Stadt en Lande
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Equipagie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aankleve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinsereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jovis	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	Jovis den 10. Maart 1718
den	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Maart	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1718	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
OGEdelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Articul	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Propositie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landtdaghs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reces	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deser	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Equipagie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aankleve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bescherminge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versekeringe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
navigatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commercie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingezetenen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ingezetenen van den Staat in de Oostzee
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oostzee	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Oostzee
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Petitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
millioenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhooghde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veylgeldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negotiatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cassa	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
helfte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerembourseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyze	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naderhandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedetermineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Stadt en Lande
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
equipagie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconsenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
expres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bedingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belastinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
