Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
185	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Borgermeesters	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Borgermeesters, Commissarissen ën Regenten van Beeck, Lande van Valckenburgb
,	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Commissarissen	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ën	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Regenten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Beeck	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Beeck, Lande van Valckenburgb
,	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Valckenburgb	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Partage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gemeentenaaren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gemeentenaaren
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reedenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Administrateurs	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Administrateurs der Landcommanderye Goederen
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landcommanderye	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghterstallige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schattingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boendergetal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sestigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boenderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	haar Hoogh Mogende Resolutie van den vyftienden Maart lestleeden
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
vyftienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	vyftienden Maart lestleeden
Maart	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
lestleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schattingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vry	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exempt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
openstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoofdbancke	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Hoofdbancke Beeck
Beeck	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geheele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Land	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Land van Valckenburgh
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Valckenburgh	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangewend	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geheele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Land	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omgeslaagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wanneer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
suleks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gemeentenaaren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gemeentenaaren van Beeck
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Beeck	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Beeck
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevalle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Octroy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pro	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
interim	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghterftallige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schattingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boendergetal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landcommanderye	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Landcommanderye
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Banck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
per	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cento	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negotieeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
capitaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vystien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangewende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schulden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noghtans	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bancke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
capitaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reysen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redimeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aflossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negotiatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conditioneeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neemende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gemeentenaaren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gemeentenaaren
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beloovende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogelijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
menage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
traghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schaaden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onkosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoedigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
booven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
