Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
In	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliberatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnderf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vsoecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
committeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hin	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	hin van Ommeren
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ommeren	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ommeren
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ripperse	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Stavenisse	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
kien	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
velsen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Schulenboeck	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bescheijden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Beden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Matthijs	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Matthijs van Risinckhoven, & Constrijeh
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Risinckhoven	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Constrijeh	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgrs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
postmr	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	postmr
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Peeter	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Clets	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
licht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
informenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veeringen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hungenoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hrnafgesant	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	hrnafgesant van Saleee
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saleee	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saleee
vdaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Boden	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Boden & post knecht
&	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
knecht	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesecludeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blijven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beure	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reijsen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
luoratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ckinctien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resol	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijtgegeprssonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resimptde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
