Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schapenen	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Schapenen ende Regenten van Esch, Quartiere van Oosterwyck , Meyerye van 's Hertogenbosch
ende	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Regenten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Esch	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Esch, Quartiere van Oosterwyck , Meyerye van 's Hertogenbosch
,	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Quartiere	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Oosterwyck	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Meyerye	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
'	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
s	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Hertogenbosch	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie van den veertienden Julii seventien hondert seven
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
veertienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	veertienden Julii seventien hondert seven
Julii	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
copielijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepermitteerr	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
coutinuatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduyrende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verpondinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geldende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sjaers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omslaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
parten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verpondingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
concessie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jare seventien hondert vyftien
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyftien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
expireren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
latende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authorisatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	veertienden Julii seventien hondert seven
Julii	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
stant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
grypen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jare seventien hondert vyftien
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyftien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
incluys	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nieuws	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnoch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omslaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verpondingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
