Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Sijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
concept	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brieff	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	resolutie van haer Ho:Mo: in date 19e. deses
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
date	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
19e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	19e. deses
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
ingestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	heer Churfurst van Ceulen
Churfurst	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Churfurst van Ceulen
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ceulen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ceulen
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mutatis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mutandis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Stadt Ceulen
Ceulen	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
raeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewuste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
defensions	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Westphalischen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Westphalischen Creijts
Creijts	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nae	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedane	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vercortinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
concept	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	Heeren Bronchors
Bronchors	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
voorgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Saecke	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergenoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
concept	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
communiceren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desselffs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoochwijs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consideratien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daervan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
