Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant-Collonel	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant-Collonel
Coetier	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bon
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
achtienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	achtienden deser loopende maendt
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maendt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Keyserlijcken	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Keyserlijcken Generael
Generael	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Schlick	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepasseerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maendt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	de Nederlanden
Nederlanden	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
komende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hof	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hof van Weenen
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Weenen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Weenen
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bon
gepasseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
occasie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant - Collonel
-	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Collonel	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Coetier	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
securiteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Keyserlijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Troupen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
insonderheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recruten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	de Nederlanden
Nederlanden	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
stonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
marcheren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogelijke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sorge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dragen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coetier	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Coetier
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hooge	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hooge Dom-Capittel des Aertz-Stift Keulen
Dom-Capittel	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Aertz-Stift	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Aertz-Stift Keulen
Keulen	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
verscheyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
malen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergeefs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ernst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
datze	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brugge-meester	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Brugge-meester te Bon
te	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bon	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bon
wilde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vliegende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brugh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
swaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ysgangh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beschadight	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geworden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoedighste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wilde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
repareren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
marsch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Troupen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versterckinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Armee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	de Nederlanden
Nederlanden	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Duytsche	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Duytsche Rijck
Rijck	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
stonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geretardeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewenschte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erlangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dater	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seventienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	seventienden deser
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
bereyts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bovengenoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recruten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thungensche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengelandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
korte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ineer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
specie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recreut-Paerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geordonneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bon
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rhijn	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Rhijn
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authoriteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dieswegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hooge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dom-Capittel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
interponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt-verlies	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reparatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vliegende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brugge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
marsch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Troupen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geretardeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dom-Capittel	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Dom-Capittel van Keulen
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Keulen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Keulen
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brugge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
herstelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schryven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
Bilderbeek	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengeschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Originelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leveren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhonde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
besten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seconderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
