Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thomas	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Thomas Slicher, Consul van desen Staat te Livorno
Slicher	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul van desen Staat te Livorno
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
desen	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Livorno	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Livorno
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praesenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
porten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sedert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	maandt Julii seventien hondert ses
Julii	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negenden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	negenden Maart seventien hondert sestien
Maart	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
sestien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaaldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verschoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bedragende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rijcksdaalders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hollandts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Generaliteyts	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Generaliteyts Rekenkamer
Rekenkamer	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
examineren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
liquideren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opsighte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rijcksdaalders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
abusivelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgetrocken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Generaliteyts	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Generaliteyts Rekenkamer
Rekenkamer	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliquideert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordonnantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolgelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
per	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rijcksdaalders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
competeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tnegentigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuyvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geannexeerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Generaliteyts	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Generaliteyts Rekenkamer
Rekenkamer	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
examineren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
liquideren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
