Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
30	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	30 der voorleeden maand July
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
voorleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
July	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jacobus	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jacobus en Johannes van de Wall en Compagnie, Kooplieden te Amsterdam
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Johannes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Wall	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Compagnie	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Kooplieden	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Kooplieden te Amsterdam
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Portugeesche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neutrale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lisbon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lisbon
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervoeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dusend	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Snaphaanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jacobus	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jacobus en Johannes van de Wall en Compagnie
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Johannes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Wall	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Compagnie	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepermitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschied	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Portugeesche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neutrale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lissabon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lissabon
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervoeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duisend	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Snaphaanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoege	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteit
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteit	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Borge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
driedubbelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Snaphaanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ryk	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ryk van Groot-Frittannien
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Groot-Frittannien	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derselfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhorige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domeinen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bepaalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongelukken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uitgesondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewysen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrivement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Snaphaanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
