Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ls	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pieter	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Pieter Cavallier, woonende alhier in den Hage
Cavallier	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
woonende	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	woonende alhier in den Hage
alhier	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
in	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	den Hage
Hage	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Hertogh van Saxen-Eysenach
Hertogh	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Eysenach	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Eysenach
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Agent	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Agent
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	den Hage
Hage	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualiteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
affaires	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welgedachten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Hertogh
Hertogh	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blykende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Originele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Hertogh
Hertogh	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaerne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualiteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erkent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
approbatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pieter	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Pieter Cavallier
Cavallier	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erkent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geadmitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erkent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geadmitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Agent	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Agent van den Heere Hertogh van Saxen -Eysenagh
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Hertogh van Saxen -Eysenagh
Hertogh	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen -Eysenagh
-	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Eysenagh	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëximeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plicht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaderdanigheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Onderdaen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Onderdaen van de Provincie van Hollandt ende West -Vrieslandt
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Hollandt ende West -Vrieslandt
van	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hollandt	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
West	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderworpen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
specialijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aensien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schattingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
impositien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reëel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
personeel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jurisdictie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Familie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
criminel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
civil	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
