Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brigadier	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Brigadier
Cronstrom	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huy	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Huy
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
achtienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	achtienden deser loopende maendt
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maendt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
antwoordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
achtsten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	achtsten daer te vooren
daer	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wisselinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Broeckhuysen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regiment van Rechteren
van	O	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Rechteren	O	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Rechteren
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Franschen	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Franschen Kryghsgevangen Capiteyn
Kryghsgevangen	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Botar	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regiment van Foix
van	O	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Foix	O	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Foix
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effectueren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wisselinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
swarigheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschiedt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Botar	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vryheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Broeckuysen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtineren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Franschen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Franschen Commissaris van Botar
Commissaris	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Botar	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
woordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sprack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinformeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Broeckhuysen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brigade	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Brigade Major
Major	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
proponerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Constant	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Albemarle	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Albemarle
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn -Lieutenant
-	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Berger	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Sturler	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Sturler
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
man	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gemeene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aequivalent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vryheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Franschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bouchain	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bouchain
gevangene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Breda	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Breda
gedetineerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingenieur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ingenieur
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brigadier	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Brigadier
Favart	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoewel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
propositie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volkomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geproportionneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reglement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aequivalenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
echter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derfde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toestaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wisselinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
considerabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officier	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Officier
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authorisatle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afwachten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
er	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sestien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maizieres	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maizieres op de Maes
op	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maes	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allerley	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bagagie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Equipagie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fransche	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Fransche Ambassadeurs
Ambassadeurs	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vreede-handelinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wooden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spraeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ambassadeurs	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ambassadeurs
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoonen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Voiture	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wilden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bedienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewyl	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorby	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huy	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Huy
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versekert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ambassadeurs	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ambassadeurs
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kanon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ceremonien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aendoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
incognito	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
