Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admt. tot Amsterdam
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ges	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
7e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	7e. deser
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	haer Ho:Mo: resol vanden 23. sept: lestleden
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
resol	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
23	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	23. sept: lestleden
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
sept	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
lestleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derselver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bericht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reqte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Isaacq	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Isaacq Oijens, Isaacq van Bueren, ende hierominus Vellers Coopluijden tot Amsterdam
Oijens	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Isaacq	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bueren	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
hierominus	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vellers	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Coopluijden	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Coopluijden tot Amsterdam
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinteresseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quantiteijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brandewijnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingecomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgeslagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'sedert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
2e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	2e. tot den 29e. Januarij lestleden
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
29e	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Januarij	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
lestleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inco	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
„	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijtgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedeelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buijten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sLants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
restitutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
incomende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rechten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sLants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brandewijnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
E	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	heeren van Beuckelom
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Beuckelom	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O	Beuckelom
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
stuck	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Brandewijnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
visiteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
examineren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
