Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteijt tot Amsterdam
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteijt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
achtsten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	achtsten deses
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
responsive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	derden derselver maent
derselver	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maent	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienvolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bericht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
memoriael	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heer	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	heer Ambassadeur van Spaigne
Ambassadeur	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spaigne	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Spaigne
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	dertienden Juli lestleden
Juli	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
lestleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hooch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerbij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
claecht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'excessendie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
‛	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingesetenen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ingesetenen deser Landen
deser	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commertie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
poortugael	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	poortugael
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
groot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadeel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coninck	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Coninck van Spaigne
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Spaigne	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Spaigne
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	heeren Huijghens
Huijghens	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
hooch	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
totte	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
zee	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
visiteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
examineren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
