Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	1 Juny deeses jaars 1785
Juny	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
deeses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
jaars	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
1785	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxamineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maria	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Maria Magdalena Rouvellet, meerderjaarige jonge Dogter, wonende te St. Eustatius
Magdalena	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rouvellet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
meerderjaarige	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	meerderjaarige jonge Dogter, wonende te St. Eustatius
jonge	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Dogter	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
wonende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
St	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	St. Eustatius
.	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Eustatius	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongeluk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaare 1771
1771	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wanneer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
slegts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oud	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noemende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Robbert Hamilton, en voorgeevende te zyn van de aansienlyke Famille in Engelund of Schotland
Robbert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hamilton	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	en voorgeevende te zyn van de aansienlyke Famille in Engelund of Schotland
voorgeevende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aansienlyke	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Famille	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
in	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Engelund	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Engelund
of	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Schotland	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schotland
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seduceeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
St	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	St. Eustatius
.	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eustatius	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
heimelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doorgegaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eiland	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Eiland St. Christoffel
St	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Christoffel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buiten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Seppliantes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beide	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ouders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
27	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	27 February 1771
February	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1771	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
clandestin	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongelukkig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolg	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praetense	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
30	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	30 November 1771
November	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1771	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genaamt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geworden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
John	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	John Doeke Hamilton
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hamilton	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naderhand	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebleeken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Robbert Hamilton, eigentlyk genaamt was Robbert Mitchell
Robbert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hamilton	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
eigentlyk	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
genaamt	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Robbert	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Robbert Mitchell
Mitchell	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aansienlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Famille	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geagoreert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
caracter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedrag	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbintenis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
altoos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inconvenabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deswegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Procedures	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
needer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoogst	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	hoogst der selver Resolutie van den 31 Mey 1781
der	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
31	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	31 Mey 1781
Mey	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
1781	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	's Lands Advocaaten
s	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Lands	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Advocaaten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Robbert Hamilton
Robbert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hamilton	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eiland	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Eiland St. Christoffel
St	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Christoffel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
27	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	27 February 1771
February	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1771	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
clandestinelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecontracteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecelebreert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nul	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nietig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onwaarde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ander	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behelpen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanmatigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ook	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Parthyen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contractanten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conventie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Transactie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermeld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nakominge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecondemneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelukkig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
agte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
relatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusichen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onwaardige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Verleider	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afgesneeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogtans	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uittersten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sinerten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kind	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongelukkige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Verbintenis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
egter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mindere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jiesde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aflectie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wertig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geprocreëert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaderlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Erffenisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestitueert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bestaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geringe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moederlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nalaatenschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daarenboven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blaam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
smet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onwettige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geboorte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevlekt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tesfens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrouwde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voortgesprooten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
minder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
swaarigheid	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemaakt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consideratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongetrouwd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedetailleerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reedenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onmogelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kind	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
per	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sub	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sequens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
matrimonium	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgunstiglyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behaagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kind	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
John	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	John Doeke Rouvellet
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rouvellet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
optima	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diverse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stukken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Petrekkelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoek	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Procureur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	's Lands Advocaaten
s	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Lands	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Advocaaten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weetenschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Souveraine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mugt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authoriteit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Juhn	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Juhn Doeke
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verwekt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
clandestin	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusichen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
27	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	27 February 1771
February	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1771	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Robbert Hamilton
Robbert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hamilton	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ss	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ss. Chriltostel
.	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chriltostel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
buiten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sappliantes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ouders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangegaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naderhand	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogence	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
31	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	31 Mey 1781
Mey	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1781	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nul	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nietig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onwaarde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Doeke Rovvellet
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rovvellet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zulks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguarde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebrek	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geboorte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aboleeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
af	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zullende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienvolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Doeke Rouvellet
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rouvellet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beboorlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepecheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegunt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geoctroyeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
succedeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Successie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodlanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijner	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moederlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Naastbestaanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reeds	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconsenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolg	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
midden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongepree	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
judicieert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Successie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nalaatenschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moederlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bloedverwanten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Doeke Rouvellet
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rouvellet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
competeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesustineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Erven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nakomelingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanbesterven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
succedeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkreegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
namaals	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkrygen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Testament	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andersints	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disponeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoef	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
believen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ook	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voortaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettelyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ampten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geadmitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekleeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Digniteiten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geboorenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegelaaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geagt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereputeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zulker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewonnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ware	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ook	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dood	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niettegenstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onwetiice	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nativiteit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naaste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Erfgenamen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moeders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reeds	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
succedeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Erven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Possesiien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkreegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkrygen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maniere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huwelyken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewonne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ware	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saake	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onwettige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nativiteit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoogst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nakomelingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eisschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretendeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mocen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niettegenstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Costumen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gewoonten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Observantien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemaakt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maaken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contrarie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lastende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beveelende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overzulks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magistraaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Justicieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ondersaaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mag	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
James	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	James Doeke Rouvellet
Doeke	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rouvellet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nakomelingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Actie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voege	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maniere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhaald	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rustelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vreedelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volkomentlyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eeuwiglyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genieten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebruiken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeyenisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contrarie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
want	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zulks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meening	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
