Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
Bilderbeeck	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	elfden deser loopende maandt
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaddresseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Griffier	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Griffier
Fagel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bylage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Churfurst van Keulen
Churfurst	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koopman	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Koopman
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geremitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
originele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordonnantien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ontfanger	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ontfanger Generaal
Generaal	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hogendorp	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Keulsche	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Keulsche Domcapittel
Domcapittel	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
administratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleverde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fouragie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Montportionen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pruyssische	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Troupen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedachte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Churfurstelycke Doorluchtigheyt
Churfurstelycke	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Doorluchtigheyt	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
retour	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meestbiedende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkoopen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chur	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Chur- Keulschen Generaal Grave van St. Maurice
-	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Keulschen	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Generaal	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Grave	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
St	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	St. Maurice
.	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Maurice	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduyrende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
absentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Churfurst
Churfurst	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regeringe	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regeringe te Bon
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Bon	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Bon
waarnam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaatse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koopman	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Koopman
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
Magis	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	den Haagh
Haagh	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meldende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Engelsch	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Engelsch Koopman, te Londen woonende
Koopman	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Londen	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Londen
woonende	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordonnantien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wilde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koopen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vernomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fine	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	fine Churfurstelycke Doorluchtigheyt
Churfurstelycke	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Doorluchtigheyt	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordonnantien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlies	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
licht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
per	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mformeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
