Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seecker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
memoriael	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Ambassadeur van Spaigne
Ambassadeur	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spaigne	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Spaigne
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derselver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	resolutie vanden eenentwintichsten Maij lestleden
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
eenentwintichsten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	eenentwintichsten Maij lestleden
Maij	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
lestleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
paspoorten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
detwee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebouwt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zeelandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Zeelandt
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coninck	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Coninck van Saigne
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Saigne	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Saigne
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overbrengende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
namen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteijnen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteijnen
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
notificerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaetsen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naetoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ambassadeur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ambassadeur
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verclarende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pierre	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Pierre francois Thuijs geboortich van S.Omer
francois	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Thuijs	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
geboortich	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
S.Omer	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	S.Omer
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteijn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteijn
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Schip genaemt Santissimo Sacrament
genaemt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Santissimo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Sacrament	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
end	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Schip genaemt Nostra Signora des Lopolo
genaemt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Nostra	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Signora	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Lopolo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Estieme	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Estieme de Puijdt
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Puijdt	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
geboortich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorstadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweenveertich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beijde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cadix	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Cadix
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
navale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
macht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoochstgemelten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coninck	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Coninck
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
paspoorten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cadix	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Cadix
voornoemt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
