Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Vrieslandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliberatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gecommitteerden ter Generaliteyt
Gecommitteerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Generaliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authoriseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschiedt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Edele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betasen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tachtigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ponden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koningh	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Koningh van Pruyssen
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Pruyssen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Pruyssen
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contributien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fouragie-gelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Landt van Cleef
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cleef	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
1702	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Troupes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelevert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
In	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pensioen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ponden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Prince Carel van Denemarcken
Prince	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Carel	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Denemarcken	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Denemarcken
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dedommagement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naergegevene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretensie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdom	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bisdom van Eutin
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eutin	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
In	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negotiatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ponden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Quartier	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Quartier van Veluwe
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Veluwe	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guarantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
En	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eyndelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
avanceren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
half	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
subsidie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cappittel	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Cappittel van Munster
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Munster	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Munster
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ponden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
En	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie der Heeren Gedeputeerden
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
gelast	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ed	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quota	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
promptelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fourneren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Aldus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geresolveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landtsschaps	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
huys	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	seven en twintighsten September 1706
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twintighsten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
September	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1706	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
