Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehoort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rapport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	B-COM	O	Heeren van Heuckelom
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Heuckelom	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Hooghgende	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
militaire	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
saken	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-COM	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	Resolutie commissoriaal van den tienden deser loopende maandt
commissoriaal	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	den tienden deser loopende maandt
tienden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	eenige Heeren Gecommitterden uyt den Raadt van State
Heeren	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gecommitterden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxamineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geproponeerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Vrieslandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogeende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerde Staten van hooghgemelde Provincie
Gedeputeerde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quamen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regiment van Saxen-Eysenach
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Eysenach	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Eysenach
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Battaillon van het Regiment van den Heere Prince van Nassau, Erf-Stadthouder van Vrieslandt
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heere Prince van Nassau, Erf-Stadthouder van Vrieslandt
Prince	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Nassau	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Erf-Stadthouder	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maastricht	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maastricht
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Overyssel
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Overyssel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedtgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van de Provincie van Vrieslandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onverwaght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorkomt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sake	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytsight	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytterste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerde Staten
Gedeputeerde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beletten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
specialyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aansien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen -Eysenach
-	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eysenach	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oversenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naderhandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederleght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerde Staten
Gedeputeerde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
wierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedifficulteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
llaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andermaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinsteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sorteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conformiteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Instructie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
groote	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaar	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaar sestien hondert een en vyftigh
sestien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
gearresteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedefereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
altydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sestien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onveranderlyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geobserveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geobserveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lange	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesamentlycke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bondtgenoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedisponeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
want	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afgegaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dispositie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
solemnele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overgiste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenparigheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gearresteerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Instructie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dievan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jare sestien hondert cen en vyftigh
sestien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
cen	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meester	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
makende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alles	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
los	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemaackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opsichte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebleven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytterste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
confusie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laast	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sesden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	sesden October laatstleden
October	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
laatstleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangewesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghTyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beklagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faciliteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bygebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bataillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wanneer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Vrieslandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerequireert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beantwoordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
difficulteyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemaackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorscschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
expresse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conditie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wercken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cesserende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
al	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
langh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecesseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Garnisoenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
keeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wanneer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
al	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepasseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toelaat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Vrieslandt
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangesien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meermalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangewesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochmaals	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
repeteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guarnisoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maastricht	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maastricht
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verswackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Poort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nacht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geslooten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beset	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nohc	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magazynen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pallisaden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daarom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Bysenach	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Bysenach
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytterste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodtsakelyckheytis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorslagh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gelderlandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gelderlandt
derwaarts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytvoerlyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangesien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
notoir	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
situatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Gelderlandt
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gelderlandt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
sich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevindt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regimenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Gelderlandt
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gelderlandt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nodigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Eysenach	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Eysenach
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
apparentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Gelderlandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gelderlandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerde Staten van Vrieslandt
Gedeputeerde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Eysenach	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Eysenach
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
ophouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reflexie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Vrieslandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
overtuyght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Overyssel
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Overyssel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Garnisoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoegh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Frontieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereeckent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oordeel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heren Gedeputeerde Staten van Vrieslandt
Gedeputeerde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesamentlycke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bondtgenoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten van Vrieslandt
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedefereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Overyssel	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Overyssel
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vreesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schynt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
evenwel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daarom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Frontieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
besettinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
want	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Frontieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
besettinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontbloot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sraat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
argedanckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sinnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
profyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingezetenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genieten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beweeghreden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Frontieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontblooten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
besettinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontblootinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Frontieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geattireert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maguzynen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fortificatiewercken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewaart	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faute	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlycke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aannemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volkomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volmaacktheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hersteldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
minder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waarheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewerckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongerymt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schade	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lyden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewyle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Arbeyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontbreeckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Stadt en Lande
en	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wercken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eygentlyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wercken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
securiteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Frontieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requireren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consideratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Logementen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingehuyrt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
provisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgeslagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onbekent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conditie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrieslandt
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
winter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reverteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gantsch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
convenabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebruyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoeghsaam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
concernerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
postponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veranderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Garnisoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Eysenach	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Eysenach
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhevigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
importantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
insonderheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewyle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regimenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stil	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saisoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quaadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongemack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lange	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maastricht	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maastricht
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
troubles	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Stadt en Lande
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geensints	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bekendt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alles	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rust	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
suffisant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cas	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nieuwe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opschuddinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dempen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolgelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
samen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesmelde	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	gesmelde Heeren Gedeputeerde Staten
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerde Staten
Gedeputeerde	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geensints	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Provincie van Vrieslandt
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daarom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochmaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ernstigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelde	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	hooghgemelde Heeren Staten
Heeren	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
soodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volkomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sorteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saxen-Eysenach	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Saxen-Eysenach
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magistraat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Battaillon van den Heere Prince van Nassau
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heere Prince van Nassau
Prince	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Nassau	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Nassau
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Over	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Over ssel
ssel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onfeylbaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verwaghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrouwen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wysheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bescheydencheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemeide	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
culiere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geringe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nut	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verblyf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
trecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praevaleren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conditie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Militie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
swaarste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exempel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhreeckinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
instructie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jare sestien hondert een en vyfti h
sestien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyfti	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
h	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
solemnelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gearresteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quaadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nalaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadruckelyckste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
protesteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resulteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Staten
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorsaack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochtans	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoopen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prompt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorfchreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regiment	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Battaillon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorkomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanwesende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerden van de Provincievan Vrieslandt
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Provincievan	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
versoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meyninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
intentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kraghtighste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seconderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
