Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wolffert	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Wolffert van Borsselen, Bailliu der Steede schepenen der selver Steden
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Borsselen	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Borsselen
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bailliu	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Bailliu der Steede schepenen der selver Steden
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Steede	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
schepenen	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
selver	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Steden	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ambachten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoecht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerbij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
raede	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	raede van Vlaenderen
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vlaenderen	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vlaenderen
geordonneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
‛	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
originele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penael	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
actie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geinstitueert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bailliu	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bailliu
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desselfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
substituijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geobtineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bij	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieven	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieven Weijtinck, Burger, ende — Ingeseten der Steede Neusen
Weijtinck	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Burger	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Burger, ende — Ingeseten der Steede Neusen
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
—	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ingeseten	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Steede	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Steede Neusen
Neusen	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daermede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termijnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
