Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
geconstitueert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooggemelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	heere Churfurst
Churfurst	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versogt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
difficulteijten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemoveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgeheven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijtstel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
liquidatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zelve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
munitien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereffent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geslooten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daarnevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sijne	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Sijne Churfurstelijcke Doorlugtigheijt
Churfurstelijcke	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Doorlugtigheijt	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgedragen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemoet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	heeren Staten vande particuliere provintien der Spaansche Nederlanden
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
particuliere	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
provintien	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Spaansche	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Nederlanden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Obligatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Coninglijcke Majesteijt van Spaignen
Coninglijcke	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Majesteijt	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Spaignen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Spaignen
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertigsten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	dertigsten Maij 1698
Maij	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
1698	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepasseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geextradeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derzelver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particuliere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Obligatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inkoop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
artillerije	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
munitien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstreckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingevalle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Luijd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Obligatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bestemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termijnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particuliere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
obligatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Churfurstelijcke Doorlaigtigheijt
Churfurstelijcke	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Doorlaigtigheijt	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particuliere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
obligatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijtstel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geextradeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenmaal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zake	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volkomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rigtigheijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebracht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schrijven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copije	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	resident
Hulst	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
originelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leveren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daarin	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allemeest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kragtige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
devoiren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wenden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
