Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	den Hage
Hage	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seventienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	seventienden deser
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
negenden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	negenden Julii laetstleden
Julii	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
laetstleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verachteringe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegebracht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
etablissement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contributien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdommen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Metz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Toul	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Verdun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Partyen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landau	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Landau ende Weissenburgh
ende	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Weissenburgh	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
byvoeginge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
essentiele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waerom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contributien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ernst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehanthaeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dieder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stabilieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sedert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
merckelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vigoureuse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geluckige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdommen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat'er	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
apparentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
immers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Metz	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Metz en Verdun
en	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Verdun	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
generale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
submisslie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytsluytinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
districten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landau	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Landau
contribueerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur van Rhynfelts
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rhynfelts	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Rhynfelts
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	eenige Dorpen van het Bisdom van Metz
Dorpen	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdom	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Metz	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretendeerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Landt - Grave
Landt	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Grave	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mr	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contributie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedeelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lagh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oostzyde	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	oostzyde van de Moesel
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moesel	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingezetenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebracht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nieuwe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onseeckerheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wetende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
submitteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duchfen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxeeuteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Landt-Graef van Hesien
Landt-Graef	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hesien	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Hesien
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contributie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sommatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koningh	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Koningh van Pruyssen
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pruyssen	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Pruyssen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schryven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ernstige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Landt-Graef
Landt-Graef	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
absentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regeringe	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regeringe te Cassel
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Cassel	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Cassel
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur van Rhijnfelts
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rhijnfelts	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederhouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdom	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bisdom van Mets
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mets	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontslaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gyselaers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgehaclt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moesten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vreemder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorkomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
datse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
minste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
communicatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koningh	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Koningh van Pruyssen
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pruyssen	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Pruyssen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
al	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na-jaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
1704	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedeelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdom	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bisdom van Mets
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mets	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
geset	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contributie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welckers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contributien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bisdommen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prosecutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onbekent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Landt-Graef
Landt-Graef	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goctgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verltaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Landt-Grave van Hessen-Cassel
Landt-Grave	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hessen-Cassel	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Hessen-Cassel
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regeringe	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regeringe te Cassel
te	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Cassel	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Cassel
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werwerden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
