Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Josias	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Josias Belesaigne en David d' Arnaud, Kooplieden te Amsterdam
Belesaigne	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
David	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
d	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Arnaud	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Kooplieden	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Kooplieden te Amsterdam
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geauthoriseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geinteresseerdens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Schip, genaamt de Harmonie
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
genaamt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Harmonie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecommandeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Cornelis	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Muyn	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Laadingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desselfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Laadingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Berbice	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Berbice
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyzgezeylt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tweeden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	tweeden Juny seeventien honderd aght en veertigh
Juny	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aght	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
veertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kaaper	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Kaaper l'Aimable Grener en de Vigilant
l'Aimable	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Grener	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Vigilant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brest	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Brest
opgebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	vyfden daar aan volgende
daar	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
volgende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raad	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raad der Prysen
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Prysen	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Parys	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Parys
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	elfden December des selven jaars
December	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
jaars	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Laadinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kaaper	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Kaaper Grenet
Grenet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconfisqueert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geappelleert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raad	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Raad des Koninghs, den Koningh, of wel desselfsBooghite Raad
des	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koninghs	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koningh	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desselfsBooghite	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raad	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
appel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
getermineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Versailles	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Versailles
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghtsten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	aghtsten deeser maand April
deeser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
April	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geordonneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguard	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
appel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geinteresseerdens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Schip de Harmonie
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Harmonie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desselfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Laadinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Armateurs	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Armateurs van de gemelde Kaapers
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kaapers	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Majesteyt
Majesteyt	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
decisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raad	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Raad der Prysen
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Prysen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elfien	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	elfien December seeventien honderd aght en veertigh
December	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aght	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
veertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Laadingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faveure	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontslaagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Partyen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerenvoyeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noopens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saacke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eysschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commissarissen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Commissarissen te Sr. Malo
te	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sr	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Sr. Malo
.	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malo	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoudens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noghtans	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eygenaars	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Eygenaars
verplight	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cautie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saacke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commissarissen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Commissarissen te St. Malo
te	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
St	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	St. Malo
.	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malo	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedecideert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschryvens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere de Larrey
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Larrey	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Larrey
,	O	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
haar	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	haar Hoogh Mogende Minister aan het Hof van Vranckryck
Hoogh	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Minister	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aan	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hof	I-HOE	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hof van Vranckryck
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vranckryck	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vranckryck
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commissaris	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Commissaris
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Deurse	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
St	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	St. Malo
.	O	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Malo	O	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saak	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
promptelijk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mooge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedecideert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
