Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeestere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Burgermeestere en Regeerders der Stadt 4mster - dam
en	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regeerders	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Stadt 4mster - dam
4mster	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
dam	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	elfden deser loopende maandt
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaques	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jaques Amiot, voor desen Burger en Koopman aldaar, doch t'hans te Utrecht woonende
Amiot	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
voor	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	voor desen Burger en Koopman aldaar, doch t'hans te Utrecht woonende
desen	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Burger	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Koopman	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
doch	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
t'hans	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Utrecht	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Utrecht
woonende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Johan	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Johan Barthelemey Rietman, Joseph Mesplet en lsaac le Boullenger, Burgers en Kooplieden te Amsterstam
Barthelemey	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rietman	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Joseph	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Mesplet	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
lsaac	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
le	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Boullenger	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Burgers	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Burgers en Kooplieden te Amsterstam
en	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Kooplieden	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterstam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterstam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jacob	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jacob Schelte , Cargadoor aldaar
Schelte	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Cargadoor	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Cargadoor aldaar
aldaar	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghtien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geequipeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fregat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	Fregat genaamt de Beurs van Amsterdam
genaamt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Beurs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Amsterdam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
Daniel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bellin	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemonteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dertigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bemant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sestigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koppen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diversse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koopmanschappen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eyge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reekeningh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Particulieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Barcelona	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Barcelona , Mattaro, Livorno en Genua
,	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mattaro	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Livorno	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Genua	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Texel	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Texel
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gezeylt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	den eersten Januari seventien hondert negentien
eersten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Januari	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
negentien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Marquis	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Marquis Beretti Landi, Ambassadeur van Spagne
Beretti	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Landi	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ambassadeur	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ambassadeur van Spagne
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Spagne	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Spagne
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omtrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Biscaayen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Biscaayen
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontmoet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweldige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
storm	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
water	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pompen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naauwer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Haven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corunna	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Corunna in Galicien
in	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Galicien	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
bereyckte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spaanschen	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Spaanschen Gouverneur, den Heere Marquis de Risbourgh
Gouverneur	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Marquis	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Risbourgh	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geobtineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Packhuysen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
slaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
herstelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
meende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
herladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsdoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbiedende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seggende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschieden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spaansche	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Spaansche Hof
Hof	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaslisteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul
Groesen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Request	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Request	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertoonende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schade	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ophoudingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sterck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bemant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tonnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goudts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veroorsaken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
representerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tractaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Alliantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vrundtschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Natien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
antwoordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kreegh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
harde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bejegeningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dreygementen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geset	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Consul en Capiteyn
en	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ambassadeur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ambassadeur van den Staat aan het Spaansche Hof
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staat	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spaansche	I-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Spaansche Hof
Hof	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
assistentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Marquis Beretti Landi
Marquis	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Beretti	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Landi	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weleke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verwondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toonde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulceke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongeregeltheden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vreede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beloofde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hof	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schryven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydtversuym	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maaken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanstondts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerelaxeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderwyl	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sollicitatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
continueerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beseffende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onreght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
geschiede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belooft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spaansche	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Spaansche Hof
Hof	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eyndelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sollicitratien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waghtens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
verlof	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gekregen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conditie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkopen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaatjes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kruyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
representeerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Buskruyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verplight	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cognoscementen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaatse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eghter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoodtsaackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wilde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rrys	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
alsdoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resteerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leghmaanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
siende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sleepende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geresolveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ophoudinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behandelinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
considerabele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schade	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegebraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verlooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maandtgelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Volck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bederf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornamentlijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingeladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erlangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geresolveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
klaghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deswegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschryvens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magistraat	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Magistraat van Amsterdam
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
amptshalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weygeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere vander Meer, der selver Ambassadeur aan het Hof van Spagne
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Meer	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ambassadeur	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ambassadeur aan het Hof van Spagne
aan	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hof	I-HOE	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hof van Spagne
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Spagne	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Spagne
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ilnstructie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toekomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
traghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wercken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
billijckheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangedaane	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schade	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergoedt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
insonderheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resterende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gouverneur	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gouverneur van de Coritinna
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coritinna	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Coritinna
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pleghtelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belooft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
