Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
OP	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Carel	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Carel Diderik du Moulin, Directeur Generaal van 's Lands Fortificatien
Diderik	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
du	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Moulin	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Directeur	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Directeur Generaal van 's Lands Fortificatien
Generaal	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
'	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
s	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Fortificatien	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualiteit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
er	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
woon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
herwaards	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moetende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliberatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belioorlyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepecheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Meubilen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huysraad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maastricht	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maastricht
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	's Hertogenbosch
s	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hertogenbosch	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Water	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
herwaards	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
transporteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vry	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lands	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geregtigheid	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
specificque	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lyste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschréeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exhibeerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
