Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	syn Excie
Excie	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'leger	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s'Hertogenbosch	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	s'Hertogenbosch
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
26e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	26e. deses
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versouck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weduwe	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	weduwe wijlen Ediwaert vere in syn leven Lieutenant Colonnel van heer horatio veer
wijlen	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	wijlen
Ediwaert	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
vere	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
in	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	in syn leven Lieutenant Colonnel van heer horatio veer
syn	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
leven	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant Colonnel van heer horatio veer
Colonnel	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
heer	I-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	heer horatio veer
horatio	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
veer	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
believen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kinderen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	kinderen
eenich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderhout	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weduwe	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	weduwe
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
persoone	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meubelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seureté	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
crediteuren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	crediteuren
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weduwe	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	weduwe
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	haere kinderen
kinderen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegeleyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gagie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerinne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lieutenant	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lieutenant colonel
colonel	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestorven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belanct	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seurete	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verclaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weduwe	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	weduwe
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conformité	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'lant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'addresseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerinne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
domicilie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhoopende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contentement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wedervaeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
