Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aenwesende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gedepde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jan	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jan Vanden Brouck, gewesen Licentmeester tot Nimmegen
Vanden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Brouck	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
gewesen	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	gewesen Licentmeester tot Nimmegen
Licentmeester	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Nimmegen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Nimmegen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	resolutie van sesten deses
van	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
sesten	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	sesten deses
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
persoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aensien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fauten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaetse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'adviseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorvallende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerenvoyeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorvallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nae	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rysch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fiscael	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	fiscael
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
partyen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehoort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Justitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exigentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respective	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegien
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermanen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermaent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorvallende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
debvoir	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
siet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschiet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nyet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vernomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faute	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
byden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fiscael	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	fiscael
eysch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nyet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoottringt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selffs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerinne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daervan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
byde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Instructie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegien	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegien ter Admiraliteyt
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
nyet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepriveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
