Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeckere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Davidt	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Davidt vanden Bogaerdt Borger van Amsterdam
vanden	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bogaerdt	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Borger	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Borger van Amsterdam
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belieft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualiteijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Consul binnen Nice ende villa Franca
binnen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nice	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Nice ende villa Franca
ende	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
villa	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Franca	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
J.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
albereijts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derwaerts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrocken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mette	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsdoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertreck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
procuratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neffens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geexhibeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dirck	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Dirck Geubel
Geubel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijner	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Siele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlicken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eedt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sweeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dirck	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Dirck Geubel
Geubel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eedt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Consul
believen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
addres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hartoch	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	hartoch van Savoijen
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Savoijen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Savoijen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consuls	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Consuls
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschiet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'ander	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vsoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
accorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
