Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Diedrich	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Diedrich van Helsdingen Borger tot Utrecht
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Helsdingen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Borger	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Borger tot Utrecht
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Utrecht	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Utrecht
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versouc	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
„	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhaelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
licentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
costen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ondecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevaeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegentheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abissina	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Abissina streckende by oosten Cabo de bonne esperance
streckende	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
oosten	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cabo	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
bonne	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
esperance	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
„	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alvoorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
xvije	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oostindische	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Oostindische Compnie
Compnie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aduis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bericht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommandatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
datse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hierop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
favorabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
adviseren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingevalle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hun	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevaeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerstdachs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevaeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
