Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretaris	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Secretaris
des	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bordes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pera	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Pera van Constantinopolen
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Constantinopolen	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twaalfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	twaalfden der voorleede maand
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
voorleede	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
grooten	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	grooten Vizir
Vizir	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
grooten	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	grooten Heer
Heer	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mignificq	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Festin	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weynige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dragonian	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Dragonian van de Porta
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	de Porta
Porta	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
grooten	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	grooten Vizir
Vizir	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyrheemsche	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	uyrheemsche Ministers
Ministers	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
insinueeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wenschte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
occasie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dessert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Confituuren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretaris	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Secretaris
des	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bordes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exempel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resideerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vreemde	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	vreemde Ministers
Ministers	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Engelsche	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Engelsche en Sweedsche Secretarissen
en	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sweedsche	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretarissen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dispenseeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diergelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dessert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereedheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daaghs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Festin	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dragoman	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Dragoman
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
grooten	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	grooten Vizir
Vizir	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beleeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangenoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretaris	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Secretaris
des	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bordes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beloop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dessert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Confituuren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
declareren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Secretaris	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Secretaris
des	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bordes	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerescribeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onkosten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dessert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Confituuren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Declaratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevalideert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
