Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pieter	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Pieter Morceau , een der geswooren Couriers te Brussel
Morceau	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
een	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	een der geswooren Couriers te Brussel
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
geswooren	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Couriers	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Brussel	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Brussel
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corps	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Couriers	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Couriers van Brussel
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brussel	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Brussel
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gekomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghdringende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geperst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoope	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seecker	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrouwen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertroostinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
halen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
acht	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	acht en twincighsten Mey laetstleden
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twincighsten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Mey	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
laetstleden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overgelevert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerden te Brussel
Gedeputeerden	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brussel	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Brussel
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seconderende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenmael	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beveelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerden
Gedeputeerden	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
provisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
drie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ondergangh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
