Ambassadeur	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hof	O	O	I-PER	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hof van Vrankryk
van	O	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vrankryk	O	B-LOC	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Vrankryk
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Parys	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Parys
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
28	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	28 der voorleeden maand
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
voorleeden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maand	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Grave de Vergennes
Grave	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vergennes	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Vergennes
geaddresseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
berigt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kooplieden	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Kooplieden
Imbert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lubbers	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bourdeaux	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Bourdeaux
gectablisseert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Neederlandsche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Westindische	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Westindische Colonien
Colonien	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Republicq	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fransche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
St	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	St. Domingue
.	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domingue	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bourdeaux	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bourdeaux
verwagt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoek	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Grave de Vergennes
Grave	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vergennes	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Vergennes
gevraagt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
apparentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedeeltelyk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Producten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colonien	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Colonien van de Republicq
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Republicq	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
beladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ook	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fransche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Havens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ladingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkoopen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inkoomende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsdan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Grave de Vergennes
Grave	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vergennes	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Vergennes
desselfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedagten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Minister van 's Konings Financien
Minister	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Konings	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Financien	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecommuniceert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Lestevenon van Berkenroode
Lestevenon	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Berkenroode	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Berkenroode
toegesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Antwoord	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Minister	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Minister
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vryheid	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Lestevenon van Berkenrode
Lestevenon	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Berkenrode	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Berkenrode
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerescribeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Grave de Vergennes
Grave	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Vergennes	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Vergennes
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
civile	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
termen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bedanken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prompte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vriendelyke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hollandsche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduurende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oorlog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrankryk	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vrankryk
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
komen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Producten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fransche	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Fransche en Nederlandsche Colonien in de Westindiën
en	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nederlandsche	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colonien	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Westindiën	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behandelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nationale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scheepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooger	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nationale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soorten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
