Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesamendlijcke	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	gesamendlijcke extraordinaris Boden
extraordinaris	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Boden	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Aernout	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
le	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Maire	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Hendrick	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Kieboom	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Frans	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Waersegger	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Jacob	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Kessel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Jan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Goot	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaerlijcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begunstigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ouder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewoonte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt van Staten
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordonnantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
depescheren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
