Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Charles	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Charles van Baerle
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Baerle	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Praesenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Regeringen	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Regeringen van Algiers, Tunis en Tripoli
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Algiers	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Algiers
,	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Tunis	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Tunis
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Tripoli	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Tripoli
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul van Baerle
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Baerle	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Baerle
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingekocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afgeladen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verson	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bysondere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
specialijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingehuyrt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genaemt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	den grooten Eendraght
grooten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Eendraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schipper	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schipper
Leendert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Dinges	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lissabon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lissabon
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maria	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schipper	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schipper
Robbert	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Andriesz	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Portsmouth	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Portsmouth
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waghtende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebeuren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebreck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
al	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leggen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bericht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
er	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerstdaeghs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Texel	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Texel
stondt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lissabon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lissabon
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wyders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Porte	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Porte Mahon
Mahon	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Baerle	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'sedert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgehouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Praessenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wachten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reyse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoedighsten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doenlijk	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quamen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
setten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt ter Admiraliteyt tot Amsterdam
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schryven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commanderende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Officieren
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelast	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Praesenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
roete	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afhalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Porte	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Porte Mahon
Mahon	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleyden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
benevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul van Baerle
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Baerle	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Baerle
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gevolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eerste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegentheydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afgchaeldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beneffens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Praesenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Algiers	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Algiers
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tunis	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Tunis
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tripoli	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Tripoli
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëscorteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
favorabele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dispositie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veertienden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	veertienden deser
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingedient	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienvolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermeldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Consul van Baerle
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Baerle	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Baerle
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduyrende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verblyf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Porte	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Porte Mahon
Mahon	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geaccordeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daeghs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capiteyn	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Capiteyn
vander	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Gon	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
defroyement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Consul
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gevolgh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
scheepsboort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
immers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
provisie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaeldt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinair	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tractement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
avans	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
silvere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ducatons	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
primo	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	primo Januarii aenstaende
Januarii	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aenstaende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consul	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsoo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respect	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mainteneren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAER	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter Admiraliteyt tot Amsterdam
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Admiraliteyt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengeschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Praesenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Convoy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lissabon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lissabon
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Middelandtsche	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Middelandtsche Zee
Zee	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedestineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Portsmuyden	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Portsmuyden
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lissabon	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lissabon
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afhalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Middelandtiche	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Middelandtiche Zee
Zee	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleyden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heeren Gedeputeerden van de Provincie van Hollandt ende West-Vrieslandt
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Provincie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Hollandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
West-Vrieslandt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoedighsten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verklaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
