Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeite	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Louis	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Louis Auguste Romorantin de Brieuw
Auguste	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Romorantin	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Brieuw	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Directeuren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Directeuren van de Societeit van Surinamen
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Societeit	I-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Societeit van Surinamen
van	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Surinamen	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Surinamen
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Capitein	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Capitein
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compagnie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Infanterie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Koppen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Duitschland	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Duitschland
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aanwerven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoekende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
einde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
depecheeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omnes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Populos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Officieren en Onderofficieren
en	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Onderofficieren	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recruten	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Recruten
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
transporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Duitschland	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Duitschland
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sig	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
begeeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mog	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumtie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officieren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Officieren, Onderofticieren en Recruten
,	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Onderofticieren	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recruten	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsz	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versogte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pasport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
omnes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Populos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepecheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
