Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wilbert	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Wilbert Phillips Burgermeester tot Woudrichem
Phillips	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeester	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Burgermeester tot Woudrichem
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Woudrichem	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Woudrichem
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cornelis	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Cornelis Willems woonende tot Almkerck inden Lande van — Althenar
Willems	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
woonende	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	woonende tot Almkerck inden Lande van — Althenar
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Almkerck	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Almkerck inden Lande van — Althenar
inden	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
—	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Althenar	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cornelis	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Cornelis van Bedichuysen
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bedichuysen	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Bedichuysen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versouck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerinne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhaelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
datse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respective	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
magere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
transporteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
riviere	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	riviere vande Maze in 't Landt van Althena
vande	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maze	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Althena	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geduerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dit	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Somerfausoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vetlen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
presenterende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
suffisante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cautie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lant	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lant van Althena
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Althena	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervoert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
expres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ingesetenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deser	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
accorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jegenstaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
strict	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Evodpgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytvoer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soorte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vivres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heure	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wejden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lande van Althenae
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Althenae	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alvoorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	't Comptoir der Convoyen bn Licenten tot Gorcum
t	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Comptoir	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Convoyen	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
bn	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Licenten	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gorcum	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Gorcum
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
latende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aenteyckeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerneffens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stellende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
suffisante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cautie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lande van Altena
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Altena	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verbracht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verdreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alvoorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
passeport	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s'Lants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerechticheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cas	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hiernae	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Istaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergenoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lant	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Lant van Altena
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Altena	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
getransporteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
indien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'ordre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'Lant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
men	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewoon	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dusdanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diergelycke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ossen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aff	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschieden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waervan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
