Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Angelina	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Angelina Catharina de Beyens, Douariere Frise de Stupenbergh, woonende tot Maestricht
Catharina	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Beyens	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Douariere	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Douariere Frise de Stupenbergh, woonende tot Maestricht
Frise	I-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Frise de Stupenbergh
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Stupenbergh	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
woonende	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Maestricht	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Maestricht
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gereleveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jegenwoordigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Processe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
specialyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstecq	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vonnisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoogen	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	hoogen Brabandtschen Gerechte
Brabandtschen	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gerechte	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
gedecerneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevolge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aenkleven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geadmitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnoch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gerechte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eysschen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Inventaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesterckt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliantes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overledene	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	overledene Ouders
Ouders	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met'er	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doodt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontruymt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nagelaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schiftinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
scheydinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deylinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geadmitteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particulierlyck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rekeningh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
revideren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belangh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
committimus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brabandtschen	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Brabandtschen Gerechte
Gerechte	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
WAER	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandement	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
committimus	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brabandtschen	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Brabandtschen Gerechte der Stadt Maestricht
Gerechte	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Maestricht
Maestricht	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlycke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
forma	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
