Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
ONtfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeester	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Burgermeester en Raadt der Stadt Venlo
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Venlo
Venlo	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Venlo	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Venlo
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	vyfden deser loopende maandt
deser	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
loopende	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maandt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bylagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magistraat	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Magistraat
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verval	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commercie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maaze	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maaze
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schipper	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Schipper
kunnende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Marcktichip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Venlo	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Venlo
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moudyck	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Moudyck of Moock
of	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moock	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wil	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particulier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genootsaackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Marcktschip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verpachten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cleefschen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Cleefschen Marektschipper van Moock op Venlo
Marektschipper	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	van Moock op Venlo
Moock	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Venlo	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
langer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconvenieert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Marcktschipper	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Marcktschipper van Roermonde
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Roermonde	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Roermonde
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tour	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moock	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Moock
aankomende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Venlo	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Venlo
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doch	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhindert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cleefschen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Cleefschen Marcktschipper
Marcktschipper	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
àl	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cleefsche	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Cleefsche Regeeringe
Regeeringe	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weygerigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
antwoordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beKomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breeder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogenste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorsieninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hindernisse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opgeheven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toekomende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegePraght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
