Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Johan	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Johan van Rielle
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rielle	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ferdinand	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ferdinand Damian van Sickingen, als Landcommandeur van de Ballie Aldenbiesen
Damian	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Sickingen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
als	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	als Landcommandeur van de Ballie Aldenbiesen
Landcommandeur	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Ballie	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ballie Aldenbiesen
Aldenbiesen	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dato	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sesden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	sesden November seeventien honderd vyf en veertigh
November	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
vyf	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
veertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecontinueert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Suppliants Soon
Soon	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Johan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Bernard	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Rielle	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Beneficie	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Beneficie van St. Catharine Autaar in de Kerck tot Hees
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
St	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Catharine	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Autaar	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kerck	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hees	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Hees
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proviseurschap	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Proviseurschap des Gasthuys
des	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gasthuys	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
administratie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rentmeester	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Rentmeester
Alard	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Johan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Gansneb	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Tengnagel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
blyckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authenticq	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
collatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
approbeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
PWAAR	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Renrmeester	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Renrmeester
Tengnagel	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desselfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beright	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toekoomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
