Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Chur-Furst van Mentz
Chur-Furst	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Mentz	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Mentz
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mentz	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Mentz
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ses	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	ses en twintighsten der voorlede maendt
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
twintighsten	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
voorlede	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maendt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommandatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faveur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Joode	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Joode
Salomon	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Abrahams	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleverde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Broodt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fourage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Copye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missivé	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reguard	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerequireerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegentheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oordelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Chur-Furst van Mentz
Chur-Furst	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Mentz	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Mentz
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerescribeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opl	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommandatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogelijke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reflexie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
