Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
15	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jacob	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jacob Dirck Sweertz de Landas
Dirck	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Sweertz	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Landas	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	hy Suppliant voor de eene helfte Possesseur ende Eygenaar was der vrye Heerlijckheydt van Oorschot
Suppliant	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eene	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
helfte	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Possesseur	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eygenaar	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vrye	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heerlijckheydt	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Heerlijckheydt van Oorschot
van	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oorschot	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
middele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lage	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jurisdictie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alles	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dependentien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heerlijckheydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wylen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overlede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Marten	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Marten Chriftiaan Sweerts de Landas
Chriftiaan	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Sweerts	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Landas	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
helft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
audientie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rolle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van Brabant
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Brabant	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
alhier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	den Hage
Hage	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opene	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
decreet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aftrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zegel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opentlijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verkoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geworden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederhelfte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
altijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gebleven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boesem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hertogh	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Hertogh
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dispositie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
representerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hertogh	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Hertogh van Brabant
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brabant	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Brabant
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geallegeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
helfte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heerlijckheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
af	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voornoemde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
overlede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederhelfte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicq	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
man	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ingekoght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewoonelijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Transporten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Verley	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Investitutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereyscht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ofte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andersints	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanigen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verhoor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nader	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mondelingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconvenieert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
