Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reqte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pr	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Pr. Jacobs van Embden, schipper van een scheepken genaemt Ste Pieter
.	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Jacobs	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Embden	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Embden
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
schipper	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	schipper van een scheepken genaemt Ste Pieter
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
een	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
scheepken	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	B-NAM	scheepken genaemt Ste Pieter
genaemt	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Ste	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
Pieter	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	I-NAM
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
permissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schip	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eijgen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
volck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ladinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ords	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ballast	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uijt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	de Maze
Maze	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
naer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Embden	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Embden
voornoemt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
„	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedeliberIs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rregte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collegie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Collegie ter admit tot Rotterdam
ter	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
admit	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Rotterdam	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ombericht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
advis	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schrijven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brieff	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
affgaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumptie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
