Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
presiderende	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	presiderende camer vande Westindische tot Middelborch
camer	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Westindische	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Middelborch	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Middelborch
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aldaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
27e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	27e. deses
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hierneffens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pointen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beschrjvinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
xixe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
iegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
6e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	6e Septemb
Septemb	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
eerst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
comende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
binnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Middelborch	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Middelborch
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
comen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versouck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
iegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gedepden	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Gedepden
derwaerts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daertoe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
committeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	heer Brunincx
Brunincx	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Strick	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Strick
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
commissie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nemen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
De	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heer	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	heer Ter cuylen
Ter	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
cuylen	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gecommunceert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sekere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dato	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
9e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	9e deses ouden styls
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
ouden	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
styls	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermrs	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Burgermrs. ende regierders der Stede Deventer
.	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
regierders	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stede	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Stede Deventer
Deventer	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versouck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wil	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sj	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meerder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
garnisoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verssien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dese	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gestelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
worden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raet	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raet van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versouck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
letten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcx	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nae	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegentheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	syn Excie
Excie	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s'Hertogenbosch	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	s'Hertogenbosch
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
29e	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	29e. deses
.	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
deses	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
egeen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
