Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
8	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
XL	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Johan	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Johan Hendrick Banerbeer van en tot HW'assenaer
Hendrick	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Banerbeer	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Banerbeer van en tot HW'assenaer
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
en	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
HW'assenaer	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	HW'assenaer
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaare seeventien honderd een en veertigh
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
veertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Suppliants
verzoek	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
accordeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
favorable	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschryvens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Churvorst van Keulen
Churvorst	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Churvorstelijcke Doorlughtigheyd
Churvorstelijcke	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Doorlughtigheyd	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moghte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behaagen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erlangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behooilijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prompte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
expeditie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
justitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zaacke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genoodsaackt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sententie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kamergeright	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Kamergeright van Wetzlar
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Wetzlar	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Wetzlar
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faveur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytgesprooken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Marquis	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Marquis van Westerlo
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Westerlo	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Westerlo
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhoud	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zaacke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
attentie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zoude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ophouden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kortheydshalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
refereeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaare	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	jaare seeventien honderd een en veertigh
seeventien	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
honderd	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
veertigh	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niettegenstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alle	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangewende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
devoiren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesteld	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongeluck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gehad	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ooghmerck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bereycken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
egbhter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghsten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
loueeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedgunstigheyd	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gwelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heer	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heer Churvorst van Keulen
Churvorst	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betuygen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Churfurstelijcke Doorlughtigheyd
Churfurstelijcke	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Doorlughtigheyd	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sunpliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vereeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Suppliant
vermeynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
flatteeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nadere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommandatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
faveur	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hooghgemelden	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	hooghgemelden Heere Churvorst
Heere	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Churvorst	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsnu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sucees	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zaacke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verzoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
derhalven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noghmaals	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brief	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschry	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	sijne Churvorstelijcke Doorlughtigheyd van Keulen
Churvorstelijcke	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Doorlughtigheyd	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lansberge	O	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lansberge
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schryven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goed	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andersins	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
appuyeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommandeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident van L.ansberge
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
L.ansberge	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	L.ansberge
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangeschreeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goed	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
reght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Suppliant
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andersins	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vrught	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
appuyeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommandeeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
