Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adriaen	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Adriaen Vermeere, Burgermeester der Stadt Aerdenburgh
Vermeere	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeester	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Burgermeester der Stadt Aerdenburgh
der	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Stadt	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Stadt Aerdenburgh
Aerdenburgh	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Paulyna	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Paulyna de Puyt, des selfs Huysvrouw
de	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Puyt	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
des	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	des selfs Huysvrouw
selfs	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Huysvrouw	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selver	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Octroy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eersten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
boven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laetste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliante	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beneden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytterste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wille	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoeve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Octroy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behoorlijke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
formarsal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedepescheert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vlaenderen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vlaenderen
gelegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uytterstewille	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mogen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
disponeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rechten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
