Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Johannes	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Johannes Stumphius, Predicant tot Leeuwen ende Puyffelijck
Stumphius	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Predicant	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Predicant tot Leeuwen ende Puyffelijck
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Leeuwen	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Leeuwen ende Puyffelijck
ende	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Puyffelijck	I-HOE	I-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
midtgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gemente	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Gemente van Puyffelijck
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Puyffelijck	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ampte	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ampte van Maes en Wael
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maes	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wael	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kercke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Puyffelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
1676	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vuyr	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vranckrijck	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Vranckrijck
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Assche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geleght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gemeente	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervallen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doordien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
af	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Predicants	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wooninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niettegenstaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Godts-dienst	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onbequaem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
redenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geëxprimeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supplianten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
repareren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
afgebrande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kerck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
behulpsaem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
liberale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gifte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewoone	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetheydt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zijnde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goedtgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opbouw	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kercke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
accorderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vijftigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordonnantie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
depescheren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
