Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
BY	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumptie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Resident suter
Resident	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
suter	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
klagende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
proceduyren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lazarus	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lazarus Schiller, Koopman tot Amsterdam
Schiller	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Koopman	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Koopman tot Amsterdam
tot	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Amsterdam	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Amsterdam
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van Strate
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Strate	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
begonnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cw	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rau	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
actie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corps	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chur-Palt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zische	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trouppes	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laatsten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorlogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemiliteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Catalnien	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Catalnien
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erlangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soume	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vyftigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
duysent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hondert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twee	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twintigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
guldens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
stuvers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
welcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
seght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretenderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corps	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memre	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schiller	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schiller
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
handt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gewesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gerenvoyetl	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
moge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Churfurstelycke	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Churfurstelycke Kryghv commissariaat
Kryghv	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
commissariaat	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
breder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
IS	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verstaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere Relrdent Suter
Relrdent	B-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Relrdent
Suter	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
antwoordt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toegevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sake	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebbende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedaan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
infomeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevinden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemeden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lazarus	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lazarus Schisser
Schisser	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
reedts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
twce	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Defaulten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeft	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geobtineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weldaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
declinatoire	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
exceptien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geproponeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
echter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raadt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raadt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Memorie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gepresenteert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
comparitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geordonneert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
differenten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tusschenspreken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Commissarissen	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Commissarissen
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
weghgenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resident	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Resident
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
yemant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijnentwegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
comparitie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verschenen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kunnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
saack	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Justitie	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Justitie
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
laten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alwaar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corps	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretensie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schiller	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schiller
kan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rade	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sullen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sustinerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Schiller	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Schiller
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extrajudiciele	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sollicitatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aangewendt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chur-Paltzische	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Chur-Paltzische Hof
Hof	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijne	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretensien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erlangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoewel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vruchteloos	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenstaande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
menighvuldige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschryvens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
door	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haar	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
