Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ter	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vergaderinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jacob	O	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Jacob van Zeyst
van	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Zeyst	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abt	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Abt der Abdye van Postel
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abdye	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Postel	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Postel
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conformité	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nevens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requeste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gevoeght	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geconfereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vacant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Personaetschap	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kercke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asten	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Asten, Meyerye van 's Hertogenbosch
,	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Meyerye	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hertogenbosch	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
qualiteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Heere van Lieshout
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Lieshout	I-HOE	B-LOC	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Lieshout
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ressort	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Meyerye	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Meyerye
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sulcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
krachte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
koop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Heerlijckheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voor	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengegaen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abt	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Abt ende Religieusen van Floref
ende	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Religieusen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Floref	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Floref
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgegane	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authorisatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nagevolghde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
approbatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ware	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gereformeerde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Religie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consequentelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ordres	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gequalificeert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jouissance	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Beneficie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorschreve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedane	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
collatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelieven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
approberen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordonneren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rentmeester	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Rentmeester der Geestelijcke Goederen tot 's Hertogenbosch
der	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geestelijcke	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goederen	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	's Hertogenbosch
s	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hertogenbosch	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nu	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tijdt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
zynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hem	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suppliant	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sijn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
leven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedurende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soude	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaerlijeksche	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
revenues	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
profluerende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
