Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Raedt van State
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ho	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgedragen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fortificatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bergen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Bergen op Zoom
op	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zoom	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ontrent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steenbergen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Steenbergen
sulcx	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geavanceert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'aenmemers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eersten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bedongen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
paye	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordonnantien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wierden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verleent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ontfanger	B-HOE	O	B-PER	O	O	O	O	O	Ontfanger Generael
Generael	I-HOE	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
Doubleth	O	O	I-PER	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dan	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verclaert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nyet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
konnen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betaelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vermits	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
toe	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nae	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliberatie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goetgevonden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	heeren van Hollant en Zeelant
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Hollant	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Hollant
en	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Zeelant	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Zeelant
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
desen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoucken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conformité	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorgaende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fortificatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noodich	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
comptoire	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	comptoire van Ontfanger Generael
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Ontfanger	B-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Ontfanger Generael
Generael	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
furneren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
anderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderlingen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
convenieren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ouer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respectiue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quota	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selffde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
penningen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
