Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
Ontfangen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Missive	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Neder-Rhijnsche	O	B-LOC	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Neder-Rhijnsche West-Phaelsche Creyts
West-Phaelsche	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Creyts	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Vergaderingh	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geschreven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Keulen	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Keulen
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
elfden	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	elfden der voorlede maendt Mey
der	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
voorlede	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
maendt	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
Mey	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houdende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Gedeputeerden van den Heere Grave van Reckheym
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Heere	B-HOE	O	B-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Heere Grave van Reckheym
Grave	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Reckheym	I-HOE	O	I-PER	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
notoire	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mede-Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Neder-Rhijnsche	O	B-LOC	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Neder-Rhijnsche West-Phaelsche Creyts
West-Phaelsche	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Creyts	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegenwoordige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Creyts-Vergaderingh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wederom	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
klagende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hadde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
kennen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gegeven	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verscheyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgers	B-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Burgers en Ingezetenen
en	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Ingezetenen	I-HOE	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Maestricht
Maestricht	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dewelcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Graefschap	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Graefschap Reckheym
Reckheym	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
veel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aensienlijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
erf	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
goederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
notoiclijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
besaten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vervolgens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schuldigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
waren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conforenses	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
'	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
rechtswegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
contribueren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
pretenselijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onderston	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geringhste	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wettige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oorsaeck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eygener	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
authoriteyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bevryden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versoeckende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geliefden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Burgermeesteren	B-HOE	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	Burgermeesteren
ende	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Raedt	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Stadt	O	B-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	Stadt Maestricht
Maestricht	O	I-LOC	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
serieuselijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beveelen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
datse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
meergemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Maestrightsche	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Maestrightsche Burgers
Burgers	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aenstonts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werckelijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoeninge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schuldigheyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinaris	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hoogh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mogende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eygen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nabuyrige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Territorien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
werckelijck	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
droegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
praterito	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quam	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prasenti	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
profuturo	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
onaengesien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
misschien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorwende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
maer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Creyts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
noyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaets	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vindende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
particulier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contract	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
effective	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
souden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
houden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
niet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nodigh	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
wegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gesamentlijcke	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Creyts	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selfs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
tegens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
soodanige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
nalatige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Contribuanten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
conform	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rijcks	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Creyts-Ordonnantien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sonder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verder	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
uytstel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
executie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
procederen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
