Token	Hoedanigheid	Plaats - Politieke Entiteit	Persoonsaanduiding	Organisatie	Datum	Resolutieverwijzing	Commissie	Overige Naam	Annotatie
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ve	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ly	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
£	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
plaetse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
legers	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lasten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
des	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaers	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	Jaers 1628
1628	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versocht	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daeruyt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voldoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
diuerse	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ligerdiensten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eenige	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fortificatiewercken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
verscheyden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
jaren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daerte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voorens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgaders	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
treyn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'artellerie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
schepen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
die	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somersaisoen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'selffde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jaer	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	O	O	O	Jaer 1628
1628	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hoger	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
syn	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geweest	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hier	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neffens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gelesen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	B-RES	O	O	resolutie vanden 21 decembris 1628
vanden	O	O	O	O	O	I-RES	O	O
21	O	O	O	O	B-DAT	I-RES	O	O	21 decembris 1628
decembris	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
1628	O	O	O	O	I-DAT	I-RES	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
belangende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
het	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
versochte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
consent	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
der	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
genomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
mitsgs	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geexamineert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staet	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'adsignatien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
den	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ontfr	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	Ontfr Generael opde Prouincien van Gelderlant, Utrecht ende Oueryssel
Generael	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
opde	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Prouincien	I-HOE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Prouincien van Gelderlant, Utrecht ende Oueryssel
van	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gelderlant	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Utrecht	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oueryssel	I-HOE	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
tot	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
betalinge	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respectiue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quota	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
somme	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vc	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
£	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Waerop	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gedelibereert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
synde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	O	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	heeren ordinaris Gedeputeerden vande Prouincie van Seelant
ordinaris	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Gedeputeerden	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Prouincie	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
Seelant	O	O	O	I-ORG	O	O	O	O
ouergenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
beyde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
als	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
oock	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	B-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	heeren extraords Gedepden
extraords	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gedepden	I-HOE	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
collegien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
staen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vertrecken	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
na	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Seelant	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	Seelant
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
communiceren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
eynde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sy	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
principale	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deuoiren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
doen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dat	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
haer	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
E	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
neffens	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
d'andere	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
cansenteren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prouintien	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hare	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
quota	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
inde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
voors	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vc	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
lt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
promptel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
willen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
daen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
op	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brengen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
geresolveert	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
datmen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbelt	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
vande	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
selue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Staten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
respectiuue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
met	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
een	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
serieusen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
brieff	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
sal	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
senden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prauincie	O	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O	prauincie van Vrieflt
van	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vrieflt	O	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
om	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
deselue	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
bewegen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ten	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fine	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
alsvoren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
ende	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
hebben	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
heeren	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gedepden	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
van	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
de	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
gemelte	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
prouincie	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
aengenomen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
t'selfde	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
fauerabel	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
te	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
secunderen	O	O	O	O	O	O	O	O
